[{"answer": "My humble apologies.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "You don't -- you were at the baby shower and you don't remember one was a girl and one was a boy?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "ANNON: I'm good.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Yes, it was a few things.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Did you know what happened?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I've tried to be optimistic the entire time.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Was there a moment when you thought, I'm in real trouble here?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I have to.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Are you doing that?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Oh, for so many reasons.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Why have you wanted to do that?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "She is amazing.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Now, more importantly, how is your lovely wife?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "She actually is more pleased because we're both horizontal next to each other.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "And she pleased or not very pleased that you are now horizontal for six hours more in the day?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "It was quite interesting, because when we found the news out, I was in the hospital in -- we were looking at -- watching CNN in my hospital bed, and you know, Mariah took it extremely hard, and, you know, because not only was that someone who was her peer, it's also a close friend.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Elaborate on that for me and what did you mean by that?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "It's very true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Has this whole experience for you made you reevaluate your life?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "ANNON: Not really.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Any other compliments?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "So there you go --", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "-- has managed to achieve the impossible.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Well, as a pastor, helping people, I answer a lot of questions, we do a lot of counseling.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What was the idea behind this?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Only in marriage.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "But only in marriage?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I did and I was wrong.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "So you -- you never had sex before marriage?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "I think I was selfish and I think I was being a hypocrite.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "But why was -- why should it be one rule for her and one rule for you?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I think it depends on the woman.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Do you think -- given you're so traditional, do you think a woman's place is really at home, looking after children?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Yes, we do have a section in there on contraception.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "What's your position on that?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Yes, well for me, honestly, it goes back to the Bible.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Yes, but I mean, should you be so bending with your religious positions and (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "I mean you're not your average pastor, are you?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I think we should take Jesus seriously.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Is that part of the problem?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I love people very much and it's -- it's --", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Do you think you're a tolerant kind of guy?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I've preached that we should love our neighbor, that we should accept --", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "But do you preach tolerance?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Tolerating people who may have a lifestyle or a belief that you don't agree with.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "What -- what do you mean by tolerance?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "To be honest with you, I haven't seen the whole thing.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "What did you think of that?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "The Bible says, on six occasions --", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "I mean do you think that homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I believe that all sex outside of heterosexual marriage.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "But given eighty states in America now have legalized gay marriage, that's fine, right?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Yes, I do -- I don't want to be the one to enforce those laws or go around --", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "I mean, no one's taking much account of the anti- fornication laws, are they?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "So let's get to the point where there is one day a vote, right?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Would I officiate same-sex weddings and things of that nature?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "-- right?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "I'm going to tell you, in some ways, but for the grace of God, but also for the fact that I literally had decided -- I had a choice about 12 years ago, either live down to the expectations of doctors who told me I would be in a wheelchair four years; this disease is so devastating, you may as well give up; you've got to stop working.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "How are you functioning on a daily basis now?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I have changed my diet.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "What have you done?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Pick any fruits you want and any vegetables.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "And it can be any vegetables?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "All completely healthy, all natural.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "It's all completely healthy?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Spinach.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "There's spinach in that?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "You got it.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "How are we going to fix America from a business point of view, in the way that you would with your diet?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "You mean the Rush Limbaugh?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "We remove it from the community.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "What do you do with it?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "When I'm watching those supercells go right over these small communities, I want to be here to help.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Why did you choose this road?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "It's very interesting, because in the last few days, I don't know why the media decided to deflect Rush Limbaugh's comment and put something I said two and a half years ago on Air America in this context.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Why do you say to that?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "America has been in a national depression.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "If you were an economic political doctor and you could treat America right now, what are the key things that need to be done?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "My friend, there's nothing -- there's not one thing on television that doesn't reward you and try to make you a excellent, from being the garbage man to the rattlesnake biter to the one who bit you, to the -- everybody.", "docId": "120309pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "Has the aspiration of being a celebrity now taken over almost anything else in life for young people?", "qSentId": 794}]